<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Hosting on Andrew M McCall</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/web-hosting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web Hosting on Andrew M McCall</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/web-hosting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Web Hosting Free Sites: Web Hosting For Developers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/web-hosting-free-sites-web-hosting-solutions-for-web-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/web-hosting-free-sites-web-hosting-solutions-for-web-developers/</guid>
      <description>Web Hosting Free Sites: A Guide To Free Web Hosting Solutions For Web Developers For new businesses or web developers that are just getting started, choosing affordable, reliable, and performant web hosting can be a challenging experience. The internet has become such an indispensable part of our lives that it&amp;rsquo;s hard to imagine a world without it. The internet has reshaped the way we do business and communicate, it has revolutionized the way we learn, work, and play, and it has changed the way we live our everyday lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Host A Static Website For Cheap On Bunny CDN</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/host-a-static-website-for-cheap-on-bunnycdn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/host-a-static-website-for-cheap-on-bunnycdn/</guid>
      <description>How To Host A Website On BunnyCDN We all want our web hosting to be as cheap as possible, especially when we are starting out. Often, many aspiring developers turn to shared hosting solutions to program their first static sites. This is convenient because in the beginning most developers struggle with basic tasks like connecting through ftp and uploading their site. As we progress, however, we begin to realize the limitations of shared hosting such as resource sharing and slow responses during peak times.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
