<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Development on Andrew M McCall</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/web-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web Development on Andrew M McCall</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/web-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Golang Image Resize and Golang Image Crop: Image Manipulation With Go Programming Language</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/12/golang-image-resize-and-golang-image-crop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/12/golang-image-resize-and-golang-image-crop/</guid>
      <description>An introduction to some of the very basic features of iamge cropping with Go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Create A Template Cache For Your Golang Web Application</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/create-a-template-cache-for-a-go-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/create-a-template-cache-for-a-go-application/</guid>
      <description>A beginner&amp;rsquo;s guide to create a reusable template cache for your Go web application: eveything you need to get started. For example the net/http and html/template package are part of the standard library and allow us to create full-featured web applications with just the standard library.&#xA;Template Cache In Go Web Applications: A Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Guide Getting started creating a web application with Go isn&amp;rsquo;t difficult. One area that was difficult for me was the idea of creating a template cache to serve Go template files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javascript For Countdown Timer | [VIDEO]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/javascript-for-countdown-timer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/javascript-for-countdown-timer/</guid>
      <description>A recurring problem that I need to solve for clients are counting down to an event, such as a sale or promotion. Countdown timers can help create a sense of urgency for potential leads so they are often used to instill a &amp;ldquo;fear of missing out&amp;rdquo; sense in leads.&#xA;If you wanted to, you could go a step further and pass in the DOM elements as part of the updateTime function to make it more reusable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Hosting Free Sites: Web Hosting For Developers</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/web-hosting-free-sites-web-hosting-solutions-for-web-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/web-hosting-free-sites-web-hosting-solutions-for-web-developers/</guid>
      <description>Web Hosting Free Sites: A Guide To Free Web Hosting Solutions For Web Developers For new businesses or web developers that are just getting started, choosing affordable, reliable, and performant web hosting can be a challenging experience. The internet has become such an indispensable part of our lives that it&amp;rsquo;s hard to imagine a world without it. The internet has reshaped the way we do business and communicate, it has revolutionized the way we learn, work, and play, and it has changed the way we live our everyday lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS Grid Gallery: Easy Fluid Gallery With CSS Grid and Javascript</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/css-grid-gallery-easy-fluid-gallery-with-css-and-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/css-grid-gallery-easy-fluid-gallery-with-css-and-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to create a fluid image gallery with css grid and a few lines of javascript. In the following article, we will learn how to create a grid gallery that is fluid and easy to navigate with CSS Grid and Javascript. First, we will create a container for our grid gallery. Then we will create a row of items. Finally, we need to set up a grid to contain the items in the row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom React Hook Function: Create Custom Reusable React Hooks</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/custom-react-hook-function/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/custom-react-hook-function/</guid>
      <description>If you have found yourself re-writing the same boilerplate React code over and over, You may be able to refactor that into a reusable custom React hook function that will save you time and help clean up your code a bit.&#xA;What Is A React Hook React Hooks are a new feature in React 16.8, which allow us to use state and lifecycle hooks without constructor functions. They enable us to write less code, improve testability of components , and reduce potential side effects .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>React State Array: Updating An Array That Is Stored Inside Of State</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/how-to-easily-access-previous-state-in-react-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/how-to-easily-access-previous-state-in-react-application/</guid>
      <description>State is one of the most important concepts in React. It&amp;rsquo;s what allows us to build components that manage and maintain their own data, and it also enables us to create reusable components that can be shared across projects without duplicating code. But what exactly is State, and how do we use it? A component&amp;rsquo;s state is simply a JavaScript object with properties and values. The values of these properties can be changed over time (hence the name &amp;ldquo;state&amp;rdquo;) by invoking setState().</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Things You Need To Know Before And After You Build A Website</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/5-things-you-need-to-know-before-and-after-you-build-a-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/5-things-you-need-to-know-before-and-after-you-build-a-website/</guid>
      <description>5 Ways You Can Use Your Website to Grow Your Business Websites are a great way to grow your business, but you need to make sure that they are properly maintained and optimized for this. In order to help you with that, here are five ways you can use your website for the growth of your business.&#xA;Create a blog: Blogging is a great way to create content and generate leads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Need To Know About Parallax Scrolling &amp; Javascript</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/a-complete-beginners-guide-to-parallax-scrolling-and-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/a-complete-beginners-guide-to-parallax-scrolling-and-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Everything a beginner javascript student needs to know about implementing parallax scrolling on their website. What parallax is, why use it, why not to use, and a few ways that it can be achieved.&#xA;What is parallax scrolling effects? What is parallax scrolling? If you have only come here for a parallax definition then your journey ends here: Parallax scrolling effects is a movement, one that is created by the scrolling of one layer of an image, which creates a sense of depth and keeps the audience&amp;rsquo;s eyes glued to the screen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Need To Know About Content Delivery Networks As A Beginner</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/everything-you-need-to-know-to-get-started-with-content-delivery-networks-as-a-beginner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/everything-you-need-to-know-to-get-started-with-content-delivery-networks-as-a-beginner/</guid>
      <description>Choosing a Content Delivery Network (CDN) is not a decision to be taken lightly. There are several factors to consider, and different factors apply to different types of website. This article guides you through the process of selecting a CDN and the factors you should consider.&#xA;What Is A Content Delivery Network A content delivery network (CDN) is a system of servers that delivers web pages, video, and applications to a user based on their location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Static Site Mistakes You Should Stop Making: A blog about the common mistakes people make when creating static sites.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/10-static-website-mistakes-you-should-stop-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/10-static-website-mistakes-you-should-stop-making/</guid>
      <description>When starting a business, it can be tempting to go with the &amp;ldquo;latest and greatest&amp;rdquo; web development technology. In fact, this same temptation often happens within a business even after it has launched a website. A website that has been built with a static site generator is always going to have a lower risk of being hacked. This doesn&amp;rsquo;t just mean your company will be less likely to be hacked, but you will also not have to throw away any code and start over if things do go wrong.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
