<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Andrew M McCall - Golang, Javascript, PHP, Wordpress</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Andrew M McCall - Golang, Javascript, PHP, Wordpress</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:22:02 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unit Testing Json Encode</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2024/03/unit-testing-json-encode/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:22:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2024/03/unit-testing-json-encode/</guid>
      <description>Here are my notes on testing a JSON writer for Golang that lets you wrap the response in an envelope</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golang Create a Random String</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2023/12/golang-create-a-random-string/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 19:18:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2023/12/golang-create-a-random-string/</guid>
      <description>Go&amp;rsquo;s rand package can help us easily generate a random string for when we need to ensure uniqueness with naming in our applicaton. We walkthrough the process of generating a random string using golang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go Channels Tutorial - Understanding Goroutines and Channels</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2023/12/go-channels-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2023/12/go-channels-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Go has powerful concurrency tools fully baked into the programming Language.  This post aims to explain go routines and channels so you can get started using them in your own projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call, Apply, And Bind Methods In Javascript</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2023/11/call-bind-and-apply-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2023/11/call-bind-and-apply-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Call, apply, and bind methods can be confusing for newer Javascript developers.  In this post, we break down Call, Apply, And Bind methods for newer Javascript developers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank You For Contacting Andrew M McCall</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/success/</guid>
      <description>Thank you I look forward to responding to your inquiry. For now, I hope you enjoy peace, prosperity, kindness, and love.&#xA;- Andrew</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics 4: Key Differences From Universal Analytics</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2023/02/google-analytics-4-key-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 20:44:47 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2023/02/google-analytics-4-key-differences/</guid>
      <description>My Notes From Google Skillshop Course on Google Analytics 4 On The Differences Between GA4 and Universal Analytics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vanilla Javascript Carousel Slider: A Beginner&#39;s Tutorial</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/easy-vanilla-javascript-carousel-slider-tutorial-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/easy-vanilla-javascript-carousel-slider-tutorial-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Vanilla Javascript Carousel Slider: A Beginner Slider A photo or content slider is one of the oldest, but most popular design assets one can create with javascript. Many developers will reach for popular carousel frameworks such as swiper, slick, or photoswipe. Most of the time, you don&amp;rsquo;t need so much overhead. Let&amp;rsquo;s build a slider together and see how we can build a responsive slider without using a ton of a extra javascript.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golang Image Resize and Golang Image Crop: Image Manipulation With Go Programming Language</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/12/golang-image-resize-and-golang-image-crop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/12/golang-image-resize-and-golang-image-crop/</guid>
      <description>An introduction to some of the very basic features of iamge cropping with Go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Complete SEO Checklist For Local Small Business Websites [Free SEO Audit Template]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/10/seo-checklist-for-local-small-business-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/10/seo-checklist-for-local-small-business-websites/</guid>
      <description>Demystify Search Engine Optimization by using my free SEO Checklist for Local Small Business Websites.&#xA;SEO CHECKLIST FOR LOCAL SMALL BUSINESS WEBSITES Download My Free Manual SEO Audit Template: free SEO Checklist For Local Small Business Websites&#xA;Today, I am going to show you how to conduct your first manual SEO audit on your local small business website. There is a ton of competing information out there which can confuse SEO beginners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Create A Website For Your Online Business: Small Business Website Guide</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/10/how-to-create-a-website-for-my-online-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/10/how-to-create-a-website-for-my-online-business/</guid>
      <description>Why Do You Need A Business Website? A business website is one of the most important tools you can have for promoting your company online. It is a cost-effective way to reach out to potential customers and clients, and it can help you build a strong online presence.&#xA;It can be used to showcase your products and services, provide information about your company, and even sell products and services online. If you are not sure where to start, there are many website builders and platforms that can help you build a professional website quickly and easily as well as a few DIY options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontmatter Data And Hugo Templates: How To Output Data With Hugo Static Site Generator</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/frontmatter-data-and-hugo-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/frontmatter-data-and-hugo-templates/</guid>
      <description>Hugo makes quick work of small client jobs. It can even handle structured data like coffee shop menus or restaurant pricing.&#xA;VIDEO: Creating A Coffee Shop Menu Using Frontmatter YAML and Hugo Creating A Hugo Homepage hugo new site my-coffee-shop &amp;amp;&amp;amp; cd my-coffee-shop&#xA;The first thing we are going to do is create a new Hugo website. In the config.toml file, we added a site title.&#xA;We also need to make sure we create a index.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golang Read Environment Variables From File: How To Do It [Code Snippets]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/golang-read-environment-variables-from-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/golang-read-environment-variables-from-file/</guid>
      <description>What Are Environmental Variables In Go A Cautionary Tale: My AWS Account Was Hacked And I Have A $50,000 Bill&#xA;If you have ever used an API key or database connection string, you have most likely had a need to secure some sensitive data. Environment variables are a way to achieve this. We may need to do this because certain API&amp;rsquo;s can only be called so many times and the key is a way of authorizing our requests and keeping track of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Secrets To Creating A Personal Coach Website That Converts</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/10-secrets-to-creating-a-personal-coaching-website-that-converts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/10-secrets-to-creating-a-personal-coaching-website-that-converts/</guid>
      <description>Are you thinking about starting a personal coaching business? If so, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to create a website that can attract and convert clients. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll share seven secrets to help you create a personal coach website that converts.&#xA;1. Have A Clear and Focused Website Goal For Your Perspective Personal Coaching Clients When starting a personal coaching business, one of the most important things you can do is to have a clear and focused goal for your website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cookieless Analytics: Cookieless Tracking Alternatives To Google Analytics</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/cookieless-analytics-cookieless-tracking-alternatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/cookieless-analytics-cookieless-tracking-alternatives/</guid>
      <description>Google Analytics is one of the most powerful web analytics suites on the internet today. Up until the release of Google Analytics 4, Google has relied solely on cookies to extract useful data from your website visitors.&#xA;Google Analytics 4 introduces a new way of tracking users across devices and platforms, using something called the User ID. With this new method, Google can track a single user as they move from one device to another, and even across different browsers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Traverse City Web Design Companies | A Complete Website Design List</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/top-20-web-design-agencies-in-traverse-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/top-20-web-design-agencies-in-traverse-city/</guid>
      <description>There are many great options for web design and graphic design in Northern Michigan. The area is home to a number of talented designers who can create stunning websites and graphics that will help your business stand out from the competition. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a simple website or something more complex, you&amp;rsquo;re sure to find a designer in Northern Michigan who can meet your needs.&#xA;We break down 20 web design agencies in Northern Michigan to help you make the best decision possible for your next web design project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Create A Template Cache For Your Golang Web Application</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/create-a-template-cache-for-a-go-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/create-a-template-cache-for-a-go-application/</guid>
      <description>A beginner&amp;rsquo;s guide to create a reusable template cache for your Go web application: eveything you need to get started. For example the net/http and html/template package are part of the standard library and allow us to create full-featured web applications with just the standard library.&#xA;Template Cache In Go Web Applications: A Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Guide Getting started creating a web application with Go isn&amp;rsquo;t difficult. One area that was difficult for me was the idea of creating a template cache to serve Go template files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap A New Hugo Theme From Scratch [video]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/bootstrap-a-new-hugo-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/bootstrap-a-new-hugo-theme/</guid>
      <description>A part of using Hugo is the freedom of making your own theme. In this tutorial, I will explain how to bootstrap a new Hugo theme so you can customize it exactly how you want to. I will go over verifying installation, creating a theme, telling Hugo how to use your new theme, and we walk through the very basics of setting up a theme so that the home page displays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Hugo With Chocolatey Package Manager On Windows 10 [video]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/install-hugo-on-windows-with-chocolately-package-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/install-hugo-on-windows-with-chocolately-package-manager/</guid>
      <description>Installing Hugo on Windows is easy with chocolately package manager.&#xA;For those who are not familiar, Hugo is a static website generator that can help you manage blazing fast static websites with minimal effort.&#xA;If you are on Windows, installing Hugo is easy using Chocolately Package Manager. Here are the steps we take.&#xA;Directions To Install Hugo on Windows 10 With Chocolately Package Manager Navigate to chocolately package manager&#xA;Click the &amp;ldquo;install&amp;rdquo; link which is located at the top right hand corner next to the light/dark toggle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCSS Use VS Import: How To Use @Use in SCSS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/scss-use-vs-import/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/scss-use-vs-import/</guid>
      <description>You have probably seen many times that @import is gradually being deprecated in SASS. So what is the alternative? Sass wants us to use @use which actually requires a little bit more setup but comes with the ability to namespace your sass and make it easier to maintain in larger projects.&#xA;What Is Wrong With Using @Import in SASS? I do not feel there is any better way to put this than cite the official SASS documentation:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VPS Hosting Security: A Crash Course On VPS Configuration</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/vps-hosting-security-ubuntu-20-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/vps-hosting-security-ubuntu-20-04/</guid>
      <description>VPS Hosting Security: What Do I Need To Know Self-hosting websites and web applications give you the ultimate control over your hosting but require a bit of knowledge to implement VPS Hosting Security. Have you ever tried to ssh into a shared server at hostinger only to find that they have bricked almost all essential functionality? The downfall of doing it yourself and having ultimate control is that your server will not be security-hardened out of the box.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javascript For Countdown Timer | [VIDEO]</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/javascript-for-countdown-timer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/javascript-for-countdown-timer/</guid>
      <description>A recurring problem that I need to solve for clients are counting down to an event, such as a sale or promotion. Countdown timers can help create a sense of urgency for potential leads so they are often used to instill a &amp;ldquo;fear of missing out&amp;rdquo; sense in leads.&#xA;If you wanted to, you could go a step further and pass in the DOM elements as part of the updateTime function to make it more reusable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is Blockchain Technology And How Does It Work?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/what-is-blockchain-technology-and-how-does-it-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/what-is-blockchain-technology-and-how-does-it-work/</guid>
      <description>What Is Blockchain Technolology, Ethereum, Smart Contracts: Explained Feeling confused about the blockchain, Ethereum, or smart contracts? This article aims to give a general introduction to the components and principles of the blockchain and help newcomers understand some of the terms and definitions behind this newer and exciting technology.&#xA;What is the Blockchain? The blockchain is a decentralized network of computers. Furthermore, it is continously growing in size. This is because the blockchain is designed to store a decentralized public ledger of information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 Expert Tips On How To Promote Your Small Business</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/12-expert-tips-for-promoting-your-small-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/12-expert-tips-for-promoting-your-small-business/</guid>
      <description>The tips in this article are meant to help you promote your small business. Small businesses have a lot of advantages over large enterprises, but they also have some disadvantages. One disadvantage is the lack of resources and money that larger businesses have. Without money, it can be difficult for a small business to get the same kind of exposure as a large corporation. What follows are 12 tips on how to promote your small business so that you can do just as well if not better than the big guys!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Analytics Platforms That Are Privacy Focused</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/web-analytics-platforms-that-are-privacy-focused/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/web-analytics-platforms-that-are-privacy-focused/</guid>
      <description>If you are still using Google Analytics: stop!&#xA;Google analytics is a powerful tool and the number one analytics platform used by businesses today. Upon first glance it may seem like a simple data analysis tool, but in reality it can be used to collect massive amounts of personal information on any internet user or device.&#xA;As we begin to shift away from the web 2.0 paradigm to web 3.0, it is important to take an inventory of our data collection habits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Hosting Free Sites: Web Hosting For Developers</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/web-hosting-free-sites-web-hosting-solutions-for-web-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/web-hosting-free-sites-web-hosting-solutions-for-web-developers/</guid>
      <description>Web Hosting Free Sites: A Guide To Free Web Hosting Solutions For Web Developers For new businesses or web developers that are just getting started, choosing affordable, reliable, and performant web hosting can be a challenging experience. The internet has become such an indispensable part of our lives that it&amp;rsquo;s hard to imagine a world without it. The internet has reshaped the way we do business and communicate, it has revolutionized the way we learn, work, and play, and it has changed the way we live our everyday lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Website Tutorial: How To Create A Hugo Website</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/hugo-website-tutorial-how-to-create-a-hugo-website-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/hugo-website-tutorial-how-to-create-a-hugo-website-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Hugo Website Tutorial: How To Create Your First Hugo Website Hugo is a powerful static website generator written in the GO language. It can help you create clean, modern websites that load quickly with little overhead.&#xA;[VIDEO] Hugo Tutorials 👉 [Video] How To Install Hugo On Windows 10 With Chocolately Package Manager (Less Than 2.5 Minutes) 👉 [Video] How To Boostrap A New Hugo Theme And Display The Home Page 👉 [Video] Output Structured Data Using Hugo, YAML, and Frontmatter What is the Hugo static site framework?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS Grid Gallery: Easy Fluid Gallery With CSS Grid and Javascript</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/css-grid-gallery-easy-fluid-gallery-with-css-and-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/css-grid-gallery-easy-fluid-gallery-with-css-and-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to create a fluid image gallery with css grid and a few lines of javascript. In the following article, we will learn how to create a grid gallery that is fluid and easy to navigate with CSS Grid and Javascript. First, we will create a container for our grid gallery. Then we will create a row of items. Finally, we need to set up a grid to contain the items in the row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom React Hook Function: Create Custom Reusable React Hooks</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/custom-react-hook-function/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/custom-react-hook-function/</guid>
      <description>If you have found yourself re-writing the same boilerplate React code over and over, You may be able to refactor that into a reusable custom React hook function that will save you time and help clean up your code a bit.&#xA;What Is A React Hook React Hooks are a new feature in React 16.8, which allow us to use state and lifecycle hooks without constructor functions. They enable us to write less code, improve testability of components , and reduce potential side effects .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>React State Array: Updating An Array That Is Stored Inside Of State</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/how-to-easily-access-previous-state-in-react-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/how-to-easily-access-previous-state-in-react-application/</guid>
      <description>State is one of the most important concepts in React. It&amp;rsquo;s what allows us to build components that manage and maintain their own data, and it also enables us to create reusable components that can be shared across projects without duplicating code. But what exactly is State, and how do we use it? A component&amp;rsquo;s state is simply a JavaScript object with properties and values. The values of these properties can be changed over time (hence the name &amp;ldquo;state&amp;rdquo;) by invoking setState().</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Things You Need To Know Before And After You Build A Website</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/5-things-you-need-to-know-before-and-after-you-build-a-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/5-things-you-need-to-know-before-and-after-you-build-a-website/</guid>
      <description>5 Ways You Can Use Your Website to Grow Your Business Websites are a great way to grow your business, but you need to make sure that they are properly maintained and optimized for this. In order to help you with that, here are five ways you can use your website for the growth of your business.&#xA;Create a blog: Blogging is a great way to create content and generate leads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Trends For Traverse City Web Development In 2022</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/5-trends-for-traverse-city-web-development-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/5-trends-for-traverse-city-web-development-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to trends in web development, there is no telling what will happen with the release of new technologies and tools. It is difficult to predict what will happen in 2022, but one thing is for sure, website trends will be different with the release of new versions of Angular, React, and other technologies. The focus on user experience will start to replace search engine optimization as the most important factor in the success of a website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Reasons To Start A Business In Traverse City</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/10-reasons-to-start-a-business-in-traverse-city-michigan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/10-reasons-to-start-a-business-in-traverse-city-michigan/</guid>
      <description>We are a website development company in Traverse City, Michigan. We make websites that are perfectly suited for your business. See what we can do for your business today.&#xA;Traverse City, Michigan is a small town with the potential for growth. There are plenty of opportunities to make new connections, especially with the thriving business community. This blog will look at 10 reasons why you should start a business in Traverse City Michigan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Need To Know About Parallax Scrolling &amp; Javascript</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/a-complete-beginners-guide-to-parallax-scrolling-and-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/a-complete-beginners-guide-to-parallax-scrolling-and-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Everything a beginner javascript student needs to know about implementing parallax scrolling on their website. What parallax is, why use it, why not to use, and a few ways that it can be achieved.&#xA;What is parallax scrolling effects? What is parallax scrolling? If you have only come here for a parallax definition then your journey ends here: Parallax scrolling effects is a movement, one that is created by the scrolling of one layer of an image, which creates a sense of depth and keeps the audience&amp;rsquo;s eyes glued to the screen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Need To Know About Content Delivery Networks As A Beginner</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/everything-you-need-to-know-to-get-started-with-content-delivery-networks-as-a-beginner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/everything-you-need-to-know-to-get-started-with-content-delivery-networks-as-a-beginner/</guid>
      <description>Choosing a Content Delivery Network (CDN) is not a decision to be taken lightly. There are several factors to consider, and different factors apply to different types of website. This article guides you through the process of selecting a CDN and the factors you should consider.&#xA;What Is A Content Delivery Network A content delivery network (CDN) is a system of servers that delivers web pages, video, and applications to a user based on their location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax For Quick Development and Fast Content Creation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/markdown-syntax-for-quick-development-and-fast-content-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/markdown-syntax-for-quick-development-and-fast-content-creation/</guid>
      <description>Markdown is a markup language developed to be easy for writers to write. It allows writers to generate web pages quickly with excellent readability. It&amp;rsquo;s main purpose is to keep things simple and straightforward so that the writer can focus on the content rather than formatting. Markdown syntax is an alternative to HTML. It is not as powerful, but in some cases, it may be easier for a writer who doesn&amp;rsquo;t know HTML (or doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to know HTML) than learning that language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Static Site Mistakes You Should Stop Making: A blog about the common mistakes people make when creating static sites.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/10-static-website-mistakes-you-should-stop-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/10-static-website-mistakes-you-should-stop-making/</guid>
      <description>When starting a business, it can be tempting to go with the &amp;ldquo;latest and greatest&amp;rdquo; web development technology. In fact, this same temptation often happens within a business even after it has launched a website. A website that has been built with a static site generator is always going to have a lower risk of being hacked. This doesn&amp;rsquo;t just mean your company will be less likely to be hacked, but you will also not have to throw away any code and start over if things do go wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Host A Static Website For Cheap On Bunny CDN</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/host-a-static-website-for-cheap-on-bunnycdn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/host-a-static-website-for-cheap-on-bunnycdn/</guid>
      <description>How To Host A Website On BunnyCDN We all want our web hosting to be as cheap as possible, especially when we are starting out. Often, many aspiring developers turn to shared hosting solutions to program their first static sites. This is convenient because in the beginning most developers struggle with basic tasks like connecting through ftp and uploading their site. As we progress, however, we begin to realize the limitations of shared hosting such as resource sharing and slow responses during peak times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Andrew M McCall and thank you for visiting my website. My website journey began in 1998 when I created my first Bon Jovi fan website (it was terrible)!&#xA;I primarily work with Go and Javascript these days. Sometimes I dive into Wordpress as well when needed.&#xA;My favorite part of developing web applications is helping to solve real world business problems.&#xA;I have worked with Javascript, Go, PHP, Wordpress, Git, SQL, Postgresql, Mongodb, and many other technologies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
