<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Static Website Generators on Andrew M McCall</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/static-website-generators/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Static Website Generators on Andrew M McCall</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/static-website-generators/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap A New Hugo Theme From Scratch [video]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/bootstrap-a-new-hugo-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/bootstrap-a-new-hugo-theme/</guid>
      <description>A part of using Hugo is the freedom of making your own theme. In this tutorial, I will explain how to bootstrap a new Hugo theme so you can customize it exactly how you want to. I will go over verifying installation, creating a theme, telling Hugo how to use your new theme, and we walk through the very basics of setting up a theme so that the home page displays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Hugo With Chocolatey Package Manager On Windows 10 [video]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/install-hugo-on-windows-with-chocolately-package-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/install-hugo-on-windows-with-chocolately-package-manager/</guid>
      <description>Installing Hugo on Windows is easy with chocolately package manager.&#xA;For those who are not familiar, Hugo is a static website generator that can help you manage blazing fast static websites with minimal effort.&#xA;If you are on Windows, installing Hugo is easy using Chocolately Package Manager. Here are the steps we take.&#xA;Directions To Install Hugo on Windows 10 With Chocolately Package Manager Navigate to chocolately package manager&#xA;Click the &amp;ldquo;install&amp;rdquo; link which is located at the top right hand corner next to the light/dark toggle.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
