<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SEO on Andrew M McCall - Golang, Javascript, PHP, Wordpress</title>
    <link>/categories/seo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SEO on Andrew M McCall - Golang, Javascript, PHP, Wordpress</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 20:44:47 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/seo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics 4: Key Differences From Universal Analytics</title>
      <link>/blog/2023/02/google-analytics-4-key-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 20:44:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2023/02/google-analytics-4-key-differences/</guid>
      <description>Google Analytics 4 vs Universal Analytics: A Comparison Measurement: Universal analytics measurement is session-based while Google Analytics 4 has a flexible event-based data model. Reporting: Universal Analytics has limited cross-device and cross-platform reporting whereas Google Analytics 4 has greater support for full cross-device and cross-platform reporting. Automation: Universal Analytics properties have limited support for automation. Google Analytics 4 supports machine learning throughout to improve and simplify insight discovery. What is An Audience?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Things You Need To Know Before And After You Build A Website</title>
      <link>/blog/5-things-you-need-to-know-before-and-after-you-build-a-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/5-things-you-need-to-know-before-and-after-you-build-a-website/</guid>
      <description>5 Ways You Can Use Your Website to Grow Your Business Websites are a great way to grow your business, but you need to make sure that they are properly maintained and optimized for this. In order to help you with that, here are five ways you can use your website for the growth of your business.
Create a blog: Blogging is a great way to create content and generate leads.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
